Everyone has a worst nlghtmare.
For some, lt's bathlng-sult season.
For others, lt's that your blrth certlflcate
can never be legally destroyed.
For Mlranda, lt was famlly hour at her gym.
What the....
Klddy Jazzerclse,
Aeroblcs Room 1, flve mlnutes.
On Sundays, her nelghborhood became
occupled terrltory under slege to chlldren.
They were everywhere.:
Movle theaters, restaurants,
bookstores, halr salons....
Starbucks was baslcally
a stroller parklng lot.
Was lt too much to hope
for one small space to call her own?
Don't touch it, pIease!
Is there a probIem?
No, it's just that
he reaIIy Iikes to push the button.
Fine, I'm in kind of a rush. Push One.
Simon, this pretty Iady said
that you couId push the button.
-So sorry.
-I'm sure it's just a phase.
Yeah, the guiIty, overinduIgent
phase of a D-I-V-O-R-C-E.
-Daddy.
-Simon, we're not being very nice to....
-That sounds Iike a princess name.
-Stop taIking.
I'm going to bite you.
-Do you want to go to the toy store Iater?
-Yes.
Then don't bite me.
I am in vioIation
of every parenting book ever written.
-Do you have kids?
-No.
Married?
-Here we are.
-At Iast.
Any chance I couId persuade you
to take another ride?
Hls name was Roger Cobb.
It only took hlm another floor and a half
to ask Mlranda for her phone number.
The whole thlng mlght have been
very romantlc...
...lf Slmon hadn't peed ln hls pants.
I don't wear vintage cIothes,
I hate fIea markets, I don't coIIect antiques.
Is it too much to ask that he not be,
I don't know, used?
Before it goes any further, just make sure
his parts are stiII under warranty.
-It's Iike chewing somebody eIse's gum.
-Divorced men do come with baggage.
Baggage is one thing.
But when they come with kids....
EspeciaIIy kids with bIadder controI issues.
Here's what I think.
Round up aII the divorced men
and keep them in a pound.
That way, you get their whoIe history
before you take one home.
If a man is divorced,
it doesn't mean he has a probIem.
Like my brother WesIey.
He just separated from his wife, LesIie--
-WesIey and LesIie? I don't think so.
-What is that, marriage by Mother Goose?
DefiniteIy a candidate for the pound.
I was going to ask you to meet him 'cause
he's coming to visit, and now forget it.
We want to meet WesIey
of WesIey and LesIie.
And p.s., does he work for NestIé?
My brother's very important to me.
I won't have him subjected
to scrutiny and ridicuIe.
-I'II be Scrutiny. You be RidicuIe.
-I aIways have to be RidicuIe.
Why can't you be RidicuIe for once?
I know.
As for me, rather than sort
through the half-off bln...
...I was datlng
someone brand-spanklng new.
I met Vaughn Welsel at a P.E.N. luncheon
a month ago.
It's amazlng how much better looklng
flctlon wrlters have become.
StiII up for a movie?
I just gotta drop these books
by my parent's pIace. It's on the way.
-GQ caIIed.
-They want you to write something?
They want me to wear something.
It's so great to be a writer these days,
there's so IittIe writing invoIved.
Don't be photographed
in anything sIeeveIess.
No one who went sIeeveIess
ever won a PuIitzer.
It's just a IittIe tip from me to you.
Nice townhouse.
-Come on in, this wiII onIy take a second.
-I'm not dressed for famiIy.
Can you just drop them
through the maiI sIot?
If I'm here and I don't say heIIo...
...I'm Iooking at two months minimum
hard famiIy time.
AII right. Yeah, okay.
Thank you.
Mother, I swear, you are the onIy person
who can kiII a cactus.
This is Carrie.
TeII your sister to stop bringing me pIants.
They get suicidaI around me.
I have to taIk them down from the Iedge.
-Those books you asked me to sign....
-Duncan, Vaughn's here.
And he brought a girI!
-Hi. WaIIis WeiseI...
-Hi.
-Have we met?
-No, I don't think so. Carrie Bradshaw.
My God. Duncan, get your ass in here.
I just Iove your coIumn.
I Iove to hear that.
-Mom, we can't stay.
-The heII you can't.
You know what you shouId write about?
Re-virginization.
Did you know there are women
who are actuaIIy having...
...their vaginas re-stitched
to make them Iike new again?
Aren't they cIever?
If you're wondering, Mom just finished
a documentary on genitaI mutiIation.
Which I stiII haven't gotten your notes on.
I toId you, I can't bring myseIf
to Iook at that thing.
And I typed aII his short stories for him
when he was 12. Duncan, Iook.
Do you know who this is?
Carrie Bradshaw.
-She writes that coIumn we Iove.
-What are you doing Thursday night?
Laundry.
I teach a seminar at CoIumbia
on CuIturaI Zeitgeist.
I'd Iove to have you come speak.
Mr. SeIf-InvoIved here
didn't teII us he was dating an icon.
-Icon?
-You are an icon. You are.
-Who brought a girI?
-This is my other sister.
Franny, this is Carrie.
-What's up?
-Hey, mom.
-Hi, sweetie.
Franny and Zooey?
What can I say?
J.D. SaIinger used to get me high.
And then she'd caII me at 3:00 a.m.,
''I Iove you.''
Good for you.
BeautifuI and she thinks I'm funny.
You're hiIarious. Put your tongue back
in your head and the Iox on the tabIe.
Come on, everybody,
Iet's have something to eat.
-We have to go.
-Come on, pIease.
We'II stay.
I mean, really,
wlthln the space of flve mlnutes...
...I had next week's column, an lnvltatlon
to speak at an Ivy League unlverslty...
...and access
to the entlre Zabar's flsh counter.
Leave now? Was he nuts?
Have you ever gone out
with someone who had a kid?
No, but I've never gone out with someone
I met on an eIevator either.
That's a first for me, too.
I met a woman on an escaIator once,
but it didn't Iast Iong.
It was over by the time
we got to Ladies Lingerie.
I dated a man once
who wore Iadies' Iingerie.
That was kind of the probIem there.
I'm kidding.
-'Cause I'm wearing panties now.
-You're kidding, right?
Look what I found.
-Can you say you're sorry?
-No!
Are you okay?
FortunateIy, I mostIy use
the right side of my brain.
It must be hard,
having a sociaI Iife as a singIe parent.
It is, I got to buy protective heImets
for aII my dates.
Where's mine, by the way?
The truth is, I didn't reaIIy have
a great sociaI Iife before Simon either.
I'm just one of those weird maIe
aberrations who prefers to be married.
I Iike stabiIity and routine. I Iike knowing
there's peopIe waiting for me at home.
-I guess that makes me sound pretty duII.
-Are you kidding?
You're the HeterosexuaI HoIy GraiI.
Mlranda wondered how a vlntage man
mlght look on her modern couch.
-Here.
-Thank you.
ProbabIy not the best time
to ask you to dinner.
Whlle Mlranda was deallng
wlth queaslness...
...Charlotte was handllng depresslon...
...whlch she felt could be solved
wlth a homemade muffln.
Here you go. Just Iike Nana used to make.
CharIie, the muffins are great,
but I'd much prefer a nice dry martini.
But Nana aIways made muffins
to cheer you up.
That was pre-LesIie. Post-LesIie,
I need a cocktaiI. Where's your vodka?
-I don't have any.
-And you caII yourseIf a Wasp.
I don't see why you two can't work it out,
you had the most beautifuI wedding.
We'II have an even IoveIier divorce.
I can't beIieve you're wiIIing
to just throw it aII away so easiIy.
ReIationships take work.
You need patience and understanding.
When was your Iast
Iong-term reIationship?
Just eat your muffin.
The afternoon had been
llke slx hours of foreplay.
Some men seduce
wlth dlm llghts and soft muslc.
Vaughn seduced
wlth chocolate chlp cookles and relatlves.
It was lnevltable thls would happen.
I just dldn't know
lt would happen so qulckly.
I'II get a tissue.
Get out now,
before he stains aII your sheets.
Come on, that's harsh.
It couId be he was just nervous.
First time is aIways weird.
-He probabIy had something to drink.
-We'd spent the day with his famiIy.
The guy couId not get
his CadiIIac into the garage.
I'm sorry, I hate being right about this.
Samantha was the General Patton of sex.
She dldn't send her troops
lnto battle lf she thought they would lose.
I Iike him.
That's sweII, but it doesn't
get the cream in the cupcake.
But the thing I Iike best about him
is his famiIy.
Anyone there you can fuck?
What? I'm trying to be heIpfuI.
I'm teIIing you, this famiIy is Iike....
They got charisma.
Like Tom Cruise,
they're the Tom Cruise of famiIies.
I'm sure the famiIy is supposed
to be the obstacIe to a reIationship...
...not the attraction.
I fucked a guy once
because his famiIy had a pooI.
He was pretty much of a nerd, but I'd go
over there and get aII cocoa-buttered up.
His mom Ioved me. She was aIways
serving me KooI-Aid and chips.
-KooI-Aid?
-Yeah, KooI-Aid, I was 13.
And honey, you shouId have seen my tan.
In my mlnd, the compllcatlons of maklng
a relatlonshlp work...
...had just expanded exponentlally.
When you date someone, how many
people become emotlonally lnvolved?
When you sleep wlth someone,
are you screwlng the famlly?
Whlle I was stlll on the fence
about Vaughn...
...I had no doubt about
my feellng for hls mother.
I was ln love wlth her.
Then we were in Nicaragua
with the Peace Corps.
That's where Vaughn was born.
I can't get over it. You've had five Iives.
I can bareIy make one happen.
Don't puII that seIf-effacing shit with me.
I see you. I know what you've got going.
What? What do I do?
I write this IittIe coIumn.
It's a contribution.
You are putting it out there.
You're part of a diaIogue.
If it wasn't for you...
...we wouIdn't know haIf the things we do
about other peopIe's sex Iives.
-Thanks a Iot.
-I'm teasing.
No, it's wonderfuI
to be frank and honest about sex.
That's how I raised my kids.
Sex was aIways a part of the discussion.
When they were 2 years oId, they knew
the proper names for their body parts.
None of this ''pee-pee''
and ''wee-wee'' crap.
And as a resuIt,
they can taIk to me about anything.
When Franny toId me she was a Iesbian...
...I said, ''Great, just as Iong
as you're not a RepubIican.''
-May I just say I Iike you very much.
-That's dear, thank you.
Did you taIk to LesIie today?
No. I taIked to her Iawyer.
Do you want to know about that?
I'm giving her the house
and she's giving me an uIcer.
I'm sorry I brought it up.
Tonight we'II have fun.
You'II finaIIy meet my friend Carrie.
We'II go out, have dinner,
maybe go to a cIub....
Shit.
This is my wonderfuI brother, WesIey.
-Nice to meet you.
-Good Iooks run in the famiIy.
-Can I get you Iadies a drink?
-CosmopoIitan.
Ditto.
-How are you enjoying New York?
-Excuse us.
Why is she here?
That's our friend.
I beIieve you remember Samantha.
You know how she gets.
Look! She's doing it aIready.
They're taIking.
Samantha says there's
a great jazz bar that we shouId go to.
-I just don't think I'm up for it tonight.
-Then maybe we'II just go.
TaIking and going to hear jazz.
I think I have your son's SIinky
embedded in my back.
I Iike to brand my women.
I'm going to use the bathroom,
and then I reaIIy wiII go.
-Daddy?
-No, Simon!
Daddy!
Shit.
I'm sorry. I was peeing,
and I didn't want him to see me.
I was afraid he'd see me...
...and then he'd be drawing pictures for
a chiId psychoIogist and nobody's happy.
-I'II get a Band-Aid.
-He's hurt. He might need a stitch.
-I'II go with you to the emergency room.
-No!
Just go.
PIease, just go.
One thlng about famllles...
...lf no one's sorry to see you go,
then you're probably not comlng back.
The next mornlng,
Charlotte was ln for a rude awakenlng.
Where do you keep your coffee fiIters?
Just teII me if I'm warm.
My brother? You sIept with my brother?
Honey, what a doII. He reaIIy--
Is your vagina
in the New York City guidebooks?
It shouId be, it's the hottest spot in town!
It's aIways open!
What's going on?
What did you say?
She was in my kitchen,
she was wearing your shirt, I snapped.
Who asked you to butt your nose
into my.... Samantha, wait! Don't go!
I didn't know your mom
was nominated for an Oscar.
Best Documentary Short.
I just Iove that she stiII has
so many ambitions for herseIf.
I'm not reaIIy in the mood
to taIk about my mom.
I'm not reaIIy in the mood to taIk at aII.
Don't touch it!
What was the documentary short
about anyway?
Good, you're back.
I swear to God, if you hand me a muffin,
I'm out of here.
You don't know Samantha. I do.
She has so many notches on her bedpost,
it's aImost whittIed down to a toothpick.
It was fun.
I know.
You had your IittIe fIing, now you can
go back to LesIie and work it out.
We're not working it out.
You think you know WesIey and LesIie?
Let me teII you about WesIey and LesIie.
LesIie's frigid and before Iast night,
WesIey hadn't gotten Iaid in two years.
-My God.
-I was going out of my mind.
I've seen a pastor. I've seen a shrink.
But untiI I saw Samantha,
I didn't reaIize what I reaIIy needed: sex.
-So it was a good thing.
-It was a frigging great thing.
That Samantha....
You've reaIIy got a good friend there.
It's CharIotte.
-That was a terribIe thing I said.
-Yes, it was.
If you'II excuse me...
...I have another tour group coming
through my vagina in 10 minutes.
I'm so sorry.
-You said what you came to say?
-Wait!
I wanted to give you this.
Samantha was touched.
She reallzed
thls was Charlotte's way of saylng...
''...Thank you for fucklng my brother.''
Get in there.
Hey, kldsI Funtastlcs on Three.
Mlranda declded she had ceded
enough terrltory to the lnvadlng troops.
Do you mind?
He reaIIy Ioves to push the button.
Yeah? So do I.
That is so sexy.
You in bed with my book.
It's reaIIy great.
-Do that again.
-What, turn the page?
Baby.
Again.
Wait, stop.
Let's just take this nice and sIow.
You teII me if you're feeIing too excited
and we'II take a IittIe break.
Why?
Because I think we both
reaIIy want this to work.
I Iove that you get so turned on by me...
...and I am very turned on by you.
Maybe we've just been
in too much of a rush.
-Forget it.
-No, I don't want to forget it. Come here.
-Let's taIk about it.
-No! I don't want to taIk about it.
I think we have to.
Why does everything have to be about sex!
I am so sick of taIking about sex.
I've been taIking about it since I was 2.
So Iet's go.
My parents are expecting us.
Duncan and I went down to
the NeiI Simon Theater and spent $65--
$75.
To see a British movie star
simuIate a bIowjob.
I wonder if that's what NeiI had in mind.
-Did she show her tits?
-No. How's the pickIed herring?
It's very good.
Franny teIIs me that you two
are going camping this weekend.
-Where's the scaIIion cream cheese?
-It's out there on the tabIe.
I don't see it.
Then check the refrigerator.
-Why is he so edgy?
-I have no idea.
-Don't Iet him puII that moody shit on you.
-I know. It's such a pose.
Since he got pubIished,
he's suddenIy this tortured artist.
-Where's the cream cheese?
-It's out there.
Why buy this shit if you can't remember
the one thing that hoIds it aII together?
Let's deaI with what's reaIIy upsetting you.
ShaII we?
If everything's on the tabIe, why don't we
start with some scaIIion cream cheese?
Jenna and I looked at each other
llke two forelgners wlthout vlsas.
You know what, I think I'd better go.
I've got a deadIine.
I'II go. Thank you for Iunch, for everything.
What happened?
Everything was going so weII.
It reaIIy wasn't.
I know what it is.
His Iast girIfriend wasn't as discreet.
I don't want to get in the irony.
He writes short stories.
This has officiaIIy become too weird.
ReaIIy, in a situation Iike this,
you gotta Iaugh.
AII right, it's a probIem.
But you'II work it out.
He won't even taIk about it.
-You want me to taIk to him?
-No.
-I can't discuss this with you.
-You can! You and I can discuss anything.
So your sex Iife isn't so great. So what?
Seventy-seven percent
of aII marriages are sexIess.
Other things are so much more important,
Iike famiIy.
Then I saw that the person I really
had to break up wlth wasn't Vaughn.
It was hls mother.
I wouId stiII Iike us to be friends.
No, I mean that.
And what happens
when you meet somebody eIse?
I can teII you now, they won't have
a mother Iike me. You know that.
You know that we have something.
What we have is very speciaI.
AII right, weII.
CaII me sometime.
-I wiII.
-Sweetie.
Wallls was rlght. The most
lmportant thlng ln llfe ls your famlly.
There are days you love them,
and others you don't.
But ln the end, they're the people
you always come home to.
Sometlmes lt's the famlly you're born lnto.
And sometlmes lt's the one
you make for yourself.
-What are you doing here?
-Come here.
欲望城市
（性爱专家凯莉布雷萧）
’缺点’
每个人都有噩梦
有些人的噩梦是穿泳衣
有些人的噩梦是知道
自己的出生证明不能被销毁
对米兰达而言
她的噩梦是健身房的家庭时间
儿童爵士舞，有氧舞蹈教室
再五分钟开始
每个周日
整个社区都被儿童包围
到处都有他们的踪迹：
餐厅，书店，美容院
星巴克变成婴儿推车停车场
拥有属于自己的小空间
太奢求了吗？
-拜托，不要乱碰
-有甚么问题吗？
他喜欢按按钮
我在赶时间，按一个就好？
这位漂亮的小姐说你可以按
-很抱歉
-我确定这只是阶段性的
因为离婚感到罪恶而宠坏小孩
-爸爸
-这样很不礼貌，你是…
-米兰达
-米兰达？
-像公主的名字
-不要说话了
-我要咬你
-想不想去玩具店？
那就不要咬我
所有育儿书上写的折磨
我都受过
-你有小孩吗？
-没有
结婚了吗？
-到了
-终于
我能说服你再搭一次吗？
他叫做罗杰科伯
搭了一层楼半他才问出
米兰达的电话
要是赛门没有尿裤子
一切都很浪漫
我不穿复古服饰，不收集古董
问他是否被「用旧了」
会不会太过分？
只是为了确定他「那里」
还可以用
那就像吃别人嚼过的口香糖
-离婚的男人有拖油瓶
-他们带来了小孩
有尿失禁的小孩
把所有离婚男子集中起来
关在一起
在接受他们之前先打听好
他们的过去
不代表他有问题
我弟弟卫斯理刚和他太太
蕾丝李分居
卫斯理和蕾丝李，不会吧？
怎么？鹅妈妈故事里的人物？
绝对是集中营的候选人
我本来想邀你们跟他见面
现在算了
我们想跟「蕾丝李的老公」
卫斯理见面
他在「耐司礼」公司工作？
我弟弟对我很重要
我不希望他被人观察和奚落
我会观察他，你会奚落他
-你有时候也要懂得奚落别人
-我知道
与其在旧恋情中浮浮沉沉
我有新的约会对象了
我在作家俱乐部餐会上
认识方恩怀佐
今日的作家都变的比较好看了
-还要去看电影吗？
-我得送东西到我父母家
-GＱ杂志打电话给我
-他们邀你写作吗？
他们邀我参加服装秀
今日的作家都不写作了
不要穿著无袖拍照
穿无袖的都不会得普立兹奖
我给你的一个小告诫
-很棒的房子
-进来，我一下子就好
我穿这样不好见你家人
你不能投到信箱里吗？
我要是不进去打声招呼
我会有两个月不好过
好吧…
妈，我发誓你是唯一
能杀死仙人掌的人
-方恩
-左伊，这是凯莉
叫你妹妹不要再带植物给我了
它们不断地想自杀
我得劝它们远离架子旁
-你要我签名的书
-太棒了
-唐肯，方恩在这里
-他带了一个女孩
-华莉丝怀佐，我们见过吗？
-没有吧，凯莉布雷萧
天，唐肯，快进来
我好爱好爱你的专栏
-我好爱好爱听到别人这么说
-妈，我们不能久留
为甚么不能
你应该写写处女膜再造术
有些女人到医院
把处女膜再缝合，变回处女
真聪明，是不是？
妈才刚完成一部
生殖器毁损的纪录片
-我还没有收到你的笔记
-我没办法看那种东西
我在他十二岁时帮他
写了他的小故事
唐肯，你知道这位是谁吗？
凯莉布雷萧
-写专栏的
-你星期四晚上要做甚么？
洗衣服
我在大学教授文化思潮
我想请你演讲
「自顾自」先生没有告诉我们
他在跟偶像约会
-你真的是个偶像
-谁带女孩来了？
这是我另一个妹妹弗兰尼
这是凯莉
-怎么了？
弗兰尼和左伊？
（美国作家沙林杰的作品）
我能怎么办？
我以前太迷沙林杰了
她会半夜三点打给我说
我爱均KA
他觉得我很好笑
你极为可笑
不要长舌了，吃东西吧
来吧，我们吃点东西
我们得走了
-我们可以留下来
-太好了
就在这短短五分钟内
我想出下礼拜专栏的内容
受邀到大学演讲
到扎巴餐厅大啖鱼类美食
现在离开？他疯了吗？
你曾和有小孩的人约会吗？
没有，我也没有跟在电梯
遇到的人约会
我曾在电扶梯遇到一个女孩
但不多久就吹了
到了女内衣部门就分手了
我曾和一个穿女人内衣的
男子约会，他有问题
-开玩笑的
-我现在穿著短内裤
你开玩笑的吧？
-爸爸，你看这个
-快说对不起
你还好吗？
幸运地，我通常用右脑思考
单亲父母的社交生活
一定很艰难
-我得帮约会对象买头盔
-我的在哪里？
赛门出生以前
我的社交生活也不怎么样
我是个脱离常轨的怪人
宁可结婚
我喜欢稳定，有规律
喜欢有人等我回家
-我听起来很无趣
-说甚么傻话
你是异性恋中的圣杯
米兰达在想一个中古男人
在她现代家具上的样子
-你看，给你
-谢谢
现在邀你吃晚餐或许不是时候
当米兰达努力克制恶心的同时
夏绿蒂在赶走沮丧
她认为可以用手工松饼解决
就像奶妈以前作的一样
松饼好吃，但我宁可要马丁尼
奶妈都会做松饼替你打气
那是以前的我
我现在需要鸡尾酒
-你的伏特加在哪里？
-我没有
-你是新教徒吗？
-你们有甚么事不能解决？
-你有一场很美丽的婚礼
-我们的离婚更可爱
我不敢相信你就这样轻易丢开
一段感情需要耐心和体谅
你最近一次最长的关系
是甚么时候？
吃你的松饼吧
那个下午就像历时
六小时的前戏
有些男人用烛光和轻音乐
引诱女人
方恩用饼乾和家人引诱我
发生这种事无可避免
我只是没料到会这么快
我去拿面纸
在他弄脏你床单之前甩了他
-或许他很紧张
-第一次总是很奇怪
-可能是喝酒的关系
-我们整天跟他的家人在一起
那家伙的车开不进车库
真讨厌被我说中
没有胜算的话
莎曼珊不随便派兵
我喜欢他
他们不会在杯子蛋糕加奶油
-我最喜欢他的家人
-有可以上床的人选吗？
我试著帮你忙
他的家人…很有魅力
就像汤姆克鲁斯
家人应该是一段感情的阻碍
不是吸引
我曾因为某人家有游泳池
跟他上床，结果他是个笨蛋
我会到他家帮忙打奶泡
他妈妈爱死我了
-她拿多果汁给我喝
-多果汁？
我当时十三岁
你应该看看我古铜色的皮肤
成功经营一段感情是不容易的
现在以指数方式持续复杂化
当你跟某人约会时
有多少人在感情上受到影响？
当你跟某人上床
是不是等于跟他全家做爱？
在我还不确定
我对方恩的感觉时
我确定我喜欢他的母亲
我爱她
我们当时在尼加拉瓜
参加和平部队
-方恩就是在那里出生的
-你救了五条生命
我不可能做得到
不要轻视你自己
我知道你会有所作为
我能做甚么？
我不过写个小专栏
那就是贡献，你写文章
你是对话的一部分
要不是你，我们就不会知道
其他人的性生活
-非常谢谢你
-我在取笑你
能这样诚实地谈论性真的很棒
我就是这样养育小孩的
性教育是我们的话题之一
两岁时，他们就知道
身体各器官的正确名称
从来没有甚么小鸡鸡小鸭鸭的
所以，他们可以跟我说任何事
当弗兰尼跟我说她是同性恋
我说：很好
只要你不是共和党员
我可不可以说我很喜欢你？
你真是个甜心，谢谢你
-你有跟蕾丝李说话吗？
-没有，我跟她律师谈过
我要把房子给她
她却给我胃溃疡
很抱歉我又提起
今晚我们来放松
凯莉会过来吃晚餐…
可恶
凯莉，莎曼珊…
这是我的好弟弟，卫斯理
-很高兴见到你
-你们家族都长得很好看
-你们女士要喝点甚么？
-四海为家
-你喜欢纽约吗？
-容我们私下谈一下
她为甚么在这里？
那是我们的朋友
你还记得莎曼珊吧？
你知道她那副德行
她已经开始了
他们在说话
莎曼珊说有一个
很棒的爵士酒吧
我今晚没那个心情
我们就去吧
聊聊天，听听爵士乐
我的背后有你儿子的娃娃
我喜欢把我的女人贴标签
我去一下洗手间就走
-爸爸
-不要，赛门
-赛门
-可恶
抱歉，我在上厕所
不希望他看见我
我怕他会看见我
就不得不去看心理医生了
-我去拿OK绷
-他可能要缝针
我跟你去急诊室
你走吧
拜托，走吧
要是在一个家庭里
没有人在乎你是否离去
你或许不用再回来了
隔天早上夏绿蒂被吵醒
你咖啡滤纸放在哪里？告诉我
你跟我弟弟睡觉？
亲爱的，你真可爱
我是说，他真的很…
你的阴道有没列入旅游书中？
那可是曼哈顿最热门的据点
而且全年开放
怎么了？
-你说甚么？
-她穿你的衣服
-我突然间…
-谁要你多管闲事…
莎曼珊，不要走
我不知道你妈妈
得过奥斯卡提名
最佳短篇纪录片
我喜欢她这样胸怀抱负
我不想谈我妈妈
我根本不想聊天
不要碰它，不要碰
那部短篇纪录片有多「短」？
很好，你回来了
我发誓，要是你再给我松饼
我马上走人
你不了解莎曼珊
她的床柱使用过度
都快磨成绣花针了
很幽默
你玩也玩过了
现在可以回到蕾丝李身边
把事情解决
我们没有办法解决
你以为你知道我们的问题？
蕾丝李很严肃，昨晚以前
卫斯理已经两年没做过爱
-我的天
-我简直快疯了
我跟牧师谈过，看过心理医生
直到我遇见莎曼珊
我才知道我需要的是「性」
-所以那是件好事
-是一件很棒的事
莎曼珊…真的是个好朋友
夏绿蒂
-我说的话很过分
-一点也没错
抱歉，还有一个旅行团
要到我的阴道参观
-我真的很抱歉
-你要说的都说了？
等一下
我要给你这个
-莎曼珊很感动
-过来
那是夏绿蒂向莎曼珊说：
谢谢你跟我弟弟上床
进来
小鬼，游乐室在三楼
米兰达觉得她不想再退让了
你介意吗？他喜欢按按钮
是吗？我也是
好性感
你跟我的书在床上
真的很棒
-再一次
-甚么？翻页吗？
宝贝…
再一次
等一下，停
我们慢慢地来
要是太兴奋就告诉我
我们可以休息一下
为甚么？
因为我觉得我们都希望能成功
我是说…
我喜欢你因我「性」致勃勃
我也因你热情如火
或许我们太急了
算了
我不想算了，过来
-我们来谈谈
-我不想谈
我们必须要谈
每件事都跟性有关
我不想再谈到性
我从两岁就开始谈论性
我们走吧，我爸妈在等我们
我们去看尼尔赛门的戏剧
-花了六十五块
-七十五
看一个英国演员假装口交
我不知道那是不是尼尔的原意
-她有露奶子吗？
-没有，腌鲱鱼好吃吗？
很棒
弗兰尼说你们周末要去露营
-奶油起司在哪里？
-在桌子那边
-我没看到
-看冰箱里有没有
-他为甚么这么急躁？
-我不知道
不要让他的情绪化影响你
只要他一出书
就会变成痛苦的艺术家
-奶油起司在哪里？
-在外面
要是不知道东西放在哪
何必买这么多鬼东西？
方恩，我们来解决
让你烦心的事，好吗？
如果你希望把东西都拿到桌上
可以先拿青葱奶油起司
珍纳和我相视
就像两个没有签证的外国人
我得走了
我要赶稿子
我要走了
谢谢你的午餐和一切
发生了甚么事？一切都很好
-不，不好
-我知道是怎么回事
他的前女友没有这么谨慎
他写短篇故事
这下子真的变得太奇怪
在这种情况下，只能傻笑
好吧，那是个问题
不过你们一定能解决
他根本不愿意谈
-你要我跟他说吗？
-不要
我没有办法跟你谈这个
你跟我甚么都可以谈
你的性生活不美满又怎样？
有七成的婚姻都是无性的
其他的事更重要，例如家庭
我发现我要分手的不是方恩
而是他的母亲
我希望我们还是朋友，说真的
要是你遇见别的人呢？
他们不会有我这样的母亲
你知道我们是独一无二的
好吧，那么…
-有时间打给我
-我会的
亲爱的
华莉丝说的对
生命中最重要的是你的家人
有时候你爱他们
有时候则不然
但他们永远是你的依靠
有时候是你出生的那个家庭
有时候是你自己组的家庭
你在那里做甚么？